Jaclyn Horton

San Jose, Ca

(415) 416-7489

jaclynchorton@icloud.com

Profile

Jaclyn 'Jackie' Horton is an experienced support professional with 5+ years of combined experience supporting end users, both internal and external. Some of her strengths are troubleshooting, imaging, configuration and upgrades. Jackie considers herself a people person and has knowledge of several programming languages.

Skills

- Communicate effectively and empathically
- Installing and set up various Windows and Mac OSX operating systems
- Hardware
- Coordinate with vendors to solve a problem
- TCP/IP
- Installing applications on and using various versions of Windows (professionally), Mac OS X (professionally) and Ubuntu Linux (as a user)
- Sharing files across different platforms
- Computer troubleshooting, upgrade, maintenance and technical support
- Experience with all popular browsers, Service Now, Heat, Remedy, Jira, Git, Zoom, Apple Configurator
- Imaging computers over a network
- Install applications over the network on desktops as well as servers
- Network computers utilizing Microsoft Networking
- Set up hard drives on a Raid or mirrored drive system
- Configure Microsoft Outlook to a Microsoft Exchange Server
- Work with Active Directory (reset passwords, set up accounts, reorganize computers and users)
- Knowledge of Python, Django, Visual Basic 6.0, VB.Net, C#, C++, SQL, Java, CSS, JS, and HTML
- Written and edited batch files
- Set up rack-mounted servers
- Connected network ports to switches and routers
- Familiar with DevOps concepts
- Setting up Zoom meetings
- Provide excellent customer service and pay strong attention to detail

Experience

Robert Half contracted to Eden Information & Referral

April 2021 to March 2022

I.T. Analyst

- Provide I.T. support
- Keep systems updated, both locally and remotely
- Track and maintain I.T. inventory, dispose of EOL systems, arrange for EOL systems to be picked up.
- Distribute and set up desk phones
- Configure laptops to connect to Azure
- Work with Dell to resolve computer issues
- Configure Last Pass.
- Correcting data on web site (Word Press)
- Created inventory app utilizing Teams
- Moved inventory into new inventory app

Robert Half contracted to Amethod Public Schools

April 2021

I.T. Analyst

- Image laptops for students
- Install applications

Robert Half contracted to Ebry I.T. who contracted to Windsor Apartments

February 2021 to April 2021

I.T. Analyst

- Set up new laptops for various Windsor office locations
- Prepare old computers and other equipment to be shipped

Optimum HIT contracted to SF Department of Public Health

April 2019 to October 2019

Epic Tester

- Provide testing of workstations in preparation of Epic rollout
- Document any failures or passes of each
- Contact command line of any issues
- Verify workstations can access proper updated Horizon VDI environment
- Reset A.D. password, add permission to A.D. profile

- Mapping network printers from within Epic
- Using Service Now to create tickets and respond to tickets of user issues

Software Solutions Specialists contracted to Bayer

October 2018 to December 2018

Desktop Technical Analyst

- Set up iPads for users to use to walk through tutorial of Windows 10, be available for questions
- Push software to new laptop/manually install application
- Educate users in Windows 10
- Install patches

Veredus contracted to Caring 4 Children

December 2015 to February 2016

Desktop Technical Analyst

Setting up computers, configuring network, activating network ports, setting access points, connect Cisco ASA 5505, connected Ruckus wireless access point, editing Active Directory profiles, resetting Active Directory profile passwords, backing up profiles, restoring profiles to new computer, installing Windows updates, updating software.

Tanson contracted to Mayo Clinic

March 2013 to November 2013 and May 2014 to October 2015

Desktop Technical Analyst

• Migrate computers from Windows XP to Windows 7, provide technical support via phone, email, IM, in person and remote software, provide PC and laptop maintenance, image computers, set up applications, check in computers, enter computers into database, backup profiles and restore profiles, utilize Heat, Remedy and Service Now call management software in acknowledging, detailing, and completing assignments, order equipment, configure and provision computers, provide data to managers concerning eligibility of employees for computer upgrades, collaborated with vendors and other departments in order to resolve issues

Wide Open West

August 2005 to January 2007

Customer Support Representative

- Provide technical support to internet, voip and catv customers
- Provide billing and other customer service support
- Set up new accounts and upgrade existing accounts

Kforce contracted to various clients for short term contracts

February 2005 to August 2005

Information Technology Consultant

• Setup and install new printers on network via IP address and to uninstall old printers.

Tek Systems contracted to Jefferson County Commission

September 2004 to February 2005

Information Technology Consultant

 Set up new Dell computers on Jefferson County Commission network, install software over network, configure network settings on computer, configure email in Outlook to connect to Exchange Server, computer maintenance, including replacing hard drives, reloading operating system, configure proprietary terminal emulation program (NXView), setup printers on network

Computer Resources

August 1998 to December 2000

Computer Assembly Manager

 Assemble desktop and server computer systems, troubleshoot computer systems, maintain inventory of assembly department, supervise employees in assembly department, maintain computer assembly serial number database

Certification

Comptia

A+ Certified (grandfathered)

Education

Ashford University, Clinton, IA

Bachelor's Degree in Psychology

Herzing College, Birmingham, AL, Madison, WI

Coursework toward Bachelors in Computer Science (Approximately 3 years)

Central Alabama Comm. College, Childersburg, AL

Associates Degree in Electronics/Computer Repair Technology